animaker.com 2015-06-07

# Animaker - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Animaker want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use Animaker's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate Animaker firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how Animaker collects information from all end users of Animaker's services (the "Services") - those who access some of Animaker Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who pay subscription fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members") - what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. Animaker requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

### Introduction

You may visit the Animaker website without a need to disclose any personal information or any information of such sort. Animaker collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access various parts of Animaker's Services and the network of Web sites accessible through Animaker's Service. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use Animaker Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below. Animaker always strive to provide the best user experience and of high quality and to allow Animaker to provide the same, Animaker collects aggregate information about the use of the Services, including information about users accessing the site or viewing animations or using our Services on other sites.

### Registration

Members are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for Animaker Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. However, in instances where Animaker and a partner jointly promote the Services, Animaker may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing Animaker and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. Animaker may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names of Members). As explained in more detail below, Animaker may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services.

### Online Advertisements

Animaker displays Animaker online advertisements. Animaker share aggregated and non-identifying information about Animaker Visitors and Members collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers. Additionally, in some instances, Animaker use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements. Animaker does not share personal information about its Visitors or Members with these advertisers.

### Contests And Promotions

Animaker may organize contests, giveaways, sweepstakes or other similar promotions from time to time and do promotions on this Site. Participation in such contests organized by Animaker is voluntary and you may require sharing your personal information with us or third parties sponsoring the contest, giveaway, or promotion, if you are participating and we will use such personal information in accordance with the rules for such contest, giveaway, sweepstakes or other promotion. You are to check the rules and regulations to determine how your information will be used and shared with others. If a third party administers the contest, your participation may be subject to additional terms and conditions and that third party's privacy policy. Animaker is not responsible for such third parties. You should carefully review these third parties' terms and conditions.

### Responses To Email Inquiries

When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to Animaker, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry that Animaker receives. Animaker does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

### Voluntary Customer Surveys

Animaker may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. Animaker encourage its customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in Animaker customer surveys is voluntary.

We take the information we receive from individuals responding to Animaker Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other Animaker customers to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions. Animaker then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of Animaker services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

### Special Cases

It is Animaker's policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, Animaker may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through Animaker Services, for any reason if, in Animaker sole discretion, it is believed that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Animaker Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect Animaker and Animaker Members.

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Animaker may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage Animaker networks. If you are a Member and have created your own Personal Start Page, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non-Animaker Web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

### Animaker's Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is Animaker policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 of USA and all other applicable laws. These services are not intended for children who have not attained the age of Majority on the day of signing up. Animaker does not knowingly collect any information from children of under the age of Majority. Finally, Animaker recommends that children ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to Animaker, or to anyone else online.

### Public Forums

Please remember that any information you may disclose in Animaker Member Directory, or other public areas of Animaker Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

### ANIMAKER'S COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Animaker control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of Animaker network and systems, we cannot guarantee that Animaker security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

### How To Access Or Modify Your Information

Animaker offers Members the opportunity to access or modify information provided during registration. To access or modify such information, visit www.animaker.com or contact Animaker Customer Service Department at Email and Contact no.

### Revisions And Updates To This Policy

In order to catch up with the technology and internet's rapidly evolving nature, Animaker may need to update its Privacy Policy from time to time. If any modification is unacceptable to you, you shall cease using this Site and the Services. If you do not cease using this Site and the Services, you will be deemed to have accepted the change. Animaker reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on Animaker's website and may send registered users and email in accordance with the Agreement so that to make you aware as to what information Animaker may collect.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact:

187 E. Warm Springs Rd,  
Suite B192, Las Vegas,   
 NV, 89119 USA.  

Last Modified: May 22, 2014.
